你在一场车祸中攻略了我
You got me in an accident
现在我都怕开车
Now I'm afraid to drive
你丢下心碎的我不管
You left my heart broken
现在我都怕去爱
Now I'm afraid to love
像是我不能说这些话一样
I can’t seem to say the words
不管我有多努力
No matter how I try
多亏你我心碎了
I fell apart thanks to you
现在我只能哭
Now all I do is cry
有人说过
They say that
雨后
If you want the rainbow
才有彩虹
you gotta have the rain
但我就是不能
But I just can't go through it
再次经历这样的困难
again
你在我身上留下的创伤
All the scars you gave me
再也无法治愈
They’ll never go away
这些心魔
All of these demons
每天萦绕在我心头
They haunt me every day
你告诉我哪些人不是你的朋友
You showed me who was not a friend
你告诉我该如何去原谅
And how I must forgive
你让我病了一段时间
You took my health for a while
竟要我继续活下去
And dared me to live
有人说过
They say that
雨后
If you want the rainbow
才有彩虹
you gotta have the rain
但我就是不能
But I just can't go through it
再经历这样的困难
again
先苦
If you want the joy
后甜
first you gotta feel some pain
但我就是不能
But I just can’t go through it
再次去尝这种苦头
again
而最糟的部分
And the worst part of all
则是恐惧
is to be fearful
我足够强大到
I’m not gone quite yet
度过这样的难关了吗
but am I stronger?
难道这里面
When I take no chances
就没有一点风险
no risk at all?
难道我忘记
When I’ve forgotten how to
急转直下地放弃
free-fall?
你说
You say
雨后
If you want the rainbow
才有彩虹
you gotta have the rain
但我就是不能
But I just can't go through it
再经历这样的困难
again
我再说一次
I’ll say it again
先苦
If you want the joy
后甜
first you gotta feel some pain
但我就是不能
But I just can’t go through it
再次去尝这种苦头
again
没有耕耘
No pain
没有收获
no gain
听起来真疯狂
that sounds so insane
我再说一次
I’ll say it again
这听起来真疯狂
that sounds so insane
我就是不能去尝这种苦头
I just can’t go through it
我感到厌倦
I’m tired of it
I’m sick of it
我就是不能
I just can’t go through it
再次去尝这种苦头
again